It Looks Like Your Browser Does Not Support Javascript. This may impact different aspects of your browsing experience.

Search for:  

Privacy and Cookie Policy
=========================

Last updated: 15 December 2022

Introduction
------------

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes how CITI Program, a division of the Biomedical Research Alliance of New York LLC (“Company,” “we,” and “our”) collects, uses and shares personal data we obtain through our affiliated websites (the “Sites”). This Policy applies when you visit the Sites and/or use our related services (the “Services”). Please read the following information carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we treat it.

Particularly Important Information
----------------------------------

**WHO WE ARE:** For the purpose of applicable data protection legislation, the data controller of your personal data is CITI Program, a division of Biomedical Research Alliance of New York LLC, with offices at 1981 Marcus Avenue, Suite 210, Lake Success, NY 11042. Our Data Protection Officer (Privacy Officer) can be contacted at [privacy@citiprogram.org](mailto:privacy@citiprogram.org).

**MUST READ SECTIONS (EEA RESIDENTS):** We draw your attention in particular to the sections entitled “International Data Transfer” and “Your Rights.”

**CHANGES TO THIS POLICY:** We will post any modifications or changes to the Policy on our Sites. We reserve the right to modify the Policy at any time, so we encourage you to review it frequently. The “Last Updated” date above indicates when this Policy was last changed. If we make any material change(s) to the Policy, we will post a notice on our Sites prior to such changes(s) taking effect.

1\. Purposes of Processing
--------------------------

### **What is personal data?**

We collect information about you in a range of forms, including personal data that includes information which, either alone or in combination with other information we hold about you, identifies you as an individual. This includes, for example, your name, postal address, email address(es), and telephone number(s).

### **Why do we need your personal data?**

We will only process your personal data in accordance with applicable data protection and privacy laws. We need certain personal data in order to provide you with access to our Services. If you create a profile/register with us, you will be asked to agree to provide this information in order to access the Services. This consent provides us with the legal basis we require under applicable law to process your data. You maintain the right to withdraw such consent at any time. If you do not agree to our use of your personal data in line with this Policy, please do not use our Services.

2\. Collecting Your Personal Data
---------------------------------

We collect information about you in the following ways:

### **Information You Give Us**

This includes:

* the personal data you provide when you register to use our Services, including your‎ name, postal address, email address(es), telephone number(s), username, password and demographic information (such as your gender);
* the personal data you provide when you report a problem with our Services or when we provide you with customer support;
* the personal data you provide when you make a purchase thorough our Sites; and
* the personal data you provide when you correspond with us by phone, email, or by other means.

### **Information We Get from Others**

We may also obtain information about you from other sources. For example, if you are part of an organization that has an agreement with us for the use of our Services, we may receive some identifiable information from the organization, such as your name, title, email address(es), and phone number(s). We may add this to information provided by you.

### **Information Automatically Collected**

We automatically log information about you and your computer or mobile device when you access our Services. For example, when visiting our Services, we log your computer or mobile device operating system name and version, manufacturer and model, browser type, browser language, screen resolution, the website you visited before browsing our Sites, pages you viewed on the Sites, how long you spent on each page, and other related information about your use of and actions with respect to our Services. We collect this information about you using tracking technologies such as “cookies.” Please refer to the sections on cookies and tracking technologies below.

### **Automated Decision Making and Profiling**

We do not generally use your personal data for the purposes of automated decision-making. However, we may do so in order to fulfil obligations imposed by law, or as part of preserving the security of our Sites, in which case we will inform you of any such processing and provide you with an opportunity to object.

3\. Cookies and Related Tracking Technologies
---------------------------------------------

### **What are cookies?**

We may collect information using tracking technologies such as “cookies.” Cookies are small data files stored on the hard drive of your computer or mobile device by a website. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer or mobile device until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our Sites.

We use two broad categories of cookies: (1) first party cookies, issued directly by us to your computer or mobile device, which are used only by us to recognize your computer or mobile device when it revisits our Services; and (2) third party cookies, which are issued by service providers on our Sites, and can be used by such service providers to recognize your computer or mobile device when it visits other websites.

### **Cookies we use**

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Type of cookie** | **Purpose** |
| _Essential Cookies_ | These cookies are essential to provide you with Services available through our Sites and to enable you to use their features fully. For example, they allow you to log in to secure areas of our Sites.  Without these cookies, the Services that you have asked for cannot be provided, and we only use these cookies to provide you with those Services. |
| _Functionality  Cookies_ | These cookies allow us to remember choices you make when you visit our Sites, such as remembering your language preferences, and remembering your login details. The purpose of these cookies is to provide you with a more personal experience and to avoid you having to re-enter your preferences every time you use our Services. |
| _Analytics and Performance Cookies_ | These cookies are used to collect information about traffic to our Sites and how users use Services. The information gathered does not identify any individual visitor, though it includes IP addresses that can be used to do so. It includes the number of visitors to each Site, the websites that referred them to that Site, the pages visited and for how long, the time of day of that session, whether this is a new or repeat visit, and other similar information.   We use this information to help operate our Sites more efficiently, to gather broad demographic information, and to monitor the level of utilization of all our Services. |
| _Social Media Cookies_ | These cookies are used when you share information using a social media sharing button or “like” button related to our Services, or you link your account or engage with our content on or through a social networking website such as Facebook, Google+, LinkedIn or Twitter. The social media site will record that you have done this. |

### **Disabling cookies**

You can typically remove or reject cookies via your browser settings. In order to do this, follow the instructions provided by your browser (usually located within the “settings,” “help,” “tools,” or “edit” facilities). Many browsers are set to accept cookies until you change your settings. NOTE: Many of our Sites will not function unless cookies are enabled, and you may be prevented from accessing a Site until cookies are enabled.

Further information about cookies, including which cookies we use, how to see what cookies have been set on your computer or mobile device and how to manage and delete them, see our [Cookie FAQ](https://support.citiprogram.org/s/article/cookie-faq) and [Cookie Listing](https://support.citiprogram.org/s/article/cookie-listing) in the CITI Program Support Center.

4\. Pixel Tags and Related Tracking Technologies
------------------------------------------------

We may also use pixel tags (which are also known as web beacons and clear GIFs) on our Sites to track the actions of users of our Services. Unlike cookies, which are stored on the hard drive of your computer or mobile device by a website, pixel tags are embedded invisibly on webpages. Pixel tags measure the success of our marketing campaigns and compile statistics about usage of the Services, so that we can manage our content more effectively. The information we collect using pixel tags may be linked to your personal data.

5\. Advertising
---------------

We currently do not use other companies to serve third-party advertisements when you visit and use the Services.

We may use Remarketing with Google Analytics, Facebook, or other social media remarketing tools to advertise online. This enables third-party vendors, including Google and Facebook, to show our ads on sites across the Internet. Such third-party vendors, may use first-party cookies and third-party cookies together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to our Site. These remarketing tools do not identify you to use personally unless you respond to an advertisement that you received directly from the service. For information on how you can opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest-based ads please visit the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/) or control the use of your device identifiers by using your device’s settings options.

6\. Using Your Personal Data
----------------------------

We will not share, sell, rent, or trade your personal data with other parties without your express consent. We may use your personal data as follows:

* to operate, maintain, and improve our Sites, and our Services delivered via those Sites;
* to manage your account, including to communicate with you regarding your account, if you have an account for one of our Services;
* to respond to your comments and questions, and to provide customer service;
* to send information including technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
* with your consent, to send you marketing e-mails about upcoming promotions, and other news, including information about products and services offered by us and our affiliates, including products and services offered by other divisions of the Biomedical Research Alliance of New York LLC. You may opt-out of receiving such information at any time: such marketing emails tell you how to “opt-out.” Please note, even if you opt out of receiving marketing emails, we may still send you non-marketing emails. Non-marketing emails include those about your account with us (if you have one) and our business dealings with you;
* to process payments for our Services that you make via our Sites;
* to link or combine user information with other personal data;
* as we believe necessary or appropriate (a) to comply with applicable laws; (b) to comply with lawful requests and legal process, including to respond to requests from public and government authorities; (c) to enforce our policies; and (d) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of you or others who use our Services; and
* as described in the “Sharing of Your Personal Data” section below.

7\. Sharing Your Personal Data
------------------------------

We may share your personal data as follows:

* **Organizational Sponsors.** When an organization (educational institution, government, research sponsor, etc.) pays for or otherwise sponsors your account or use of our Services, the sponsor will be able to see your profile information and your activities, such as enrollment, participation, progress, results and completions status of training and other user information. Organizational Sponsors will also be able to see your name (not only your username) as well as your email address(es) and other contact information if you include such data in your account profile.
* **Third Parties Designated by You.** We may share your personal data with third parties but only when you have provided express consent to do so.
* **Our Third Party Service Providers.** We may share your personal data with our third party service providers who provide services such as data analysis, payment processing, information technology and related infrastructure provision, customer service, email delivery, auditing and other similar services. These third parties are only permitted to use your personal data to the extent necessary to enable them to provide their services to us. They are required to follow our express instructions and to comply with appropriate security measures to protect your personal data.
* **Affiliates.** We may share some or all of your personal data with our affiliates, including other divisions of Biomedical Research Alliance of New York LLC, in which case we will require our affiliates to comply with this Policy. In particular, you may let us share personal data with our affiliates where you wish to receive marketing communications from them.
* **Corporate Restructuring.** We may share personal data when we do a business deal, or negotiate a business deal, involving the sale or transfer of all or a part of our business or assets. These deals can include any merger, financing, acquisition, or bankruptcy transaction or proceeding.
* **Other Disclosures.** We may share personal data as we believe necessary or appropriate: (a) to comply with applicable laws; (b) to comply with lawful requests and legal process, including to respond to requests from public and government authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements; (c) to enforce this Policy or related policies; and (d) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of you or others.

8\. Anonymous Data
------------------

When we use the term “anonymous data,” we are referring to data and information that does not permit you to be identified or identifiable, either alone or when combined with any other information available to a third party.

We may create anonymous data from the personal data we receive about you and other individuals whose personal data we collect. Anonymous data might include analytics information and information collected by us using cookies or other tracking technologies. We convert personal data into anonymous data by excluding information (such as your name), and modifying any other elements that are reasonably likely to make the data personally identifiable. We use this anonymous data to analyze usage patterns in order to make improvements to our Sites and Services.

9\. Third Party Sites
---------------------

Our Sites may contain links to third-party websites and features. This Policy does not cover the privacy practices of such third parties. These third parties have their own privacy policies and we do not accept any responsibility or liability for their websites, features, or policies. Please read their privacy policies before you submit any data to them. If you believe a link has been placed on our website incorrectly, please email us at info@citiprogram.org, or you can contact our website management company, [Proper Noun](https://www.propernoun.co/).

10\. User Generated Content
---------------------------

If you provide feedback to us, we may use and disclose such feedback on our Sites, provided we do not associate such feedback with your personal data or other identifying information. If you have provided your consent to do so, we may, with your approval, post your first and last name along with your feedback about our Services on our Sites.

11\. International Data Transfer
--------------------------------

Your information, including personal data that we collect from you, may be transferred to, stored, and processed by us and our affiliates and other third parties outside the country in which you reside, including, but not limited to the United States, where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world. By using our Services, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. If you are a resident of the EEA, you will be required to confirm your acceptance of such transfer, storing or processing when you create your user account. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Policy. Please check your account settings to confirm that you have selected the security profile that best suits your needs.

12\. Security
-------------

We endeavor to use reasonable organizational, technical, and administrative measures to protect personal data within our organization. Unfortunately, no transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be completely secure, and transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. If you have reason to believe that any interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of any account you might have with us has been compromised), please immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us at [security@citiprogram.org](mailto:security@citiprogram.org) or by using the details in Section 18 below.

13\. Retention
--------------

We will only retain your personal data for as long reasonably required for us to provide you with our Services or until you close your account/cancel your subscription, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (for example for regulatory purposes), or as required by the sponsoring organization paying for your access to our Services.

14\. Our Policy on Children
---------------------------

Our Services do not knowingly create accounts for nor collect information from minors under 18 years of age without parental consent or parental notification. Subscriber Organizations creating CITI Program accounts are solely responsible for ensuring age and permission requirements for their Affiliated Learners. If you are a secondary school Subscriber Organization, please see our Secondary School Amendment at [https://about.citiprogram.org/terms-of-service-secondary-school-amendment/](https://about.citiprogram.org/terms-of-service-secondary-school-amendment/).  If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should contact us using the details in Section 18 below. We will delete such information from our files as soon as reasonably practicable. Our accounts are not knowingly provided to any persons under 13 years of age under any circumstances.

15\. Sensitive Personal Data
----------------------------

Subject to the following paragraph, we ask that you not send us, and you not disclose, any sensitive personal data (e.g., social security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, biometrics or genetic characteristics, criminal background or trade union membership) on or through our Sites or otherwise to us. We do not actively collect sensitive personal data.

If you send or disclose any sensitive personal data to us when you submit user generated content to our Services, you consent to our processing and use of such sensitive personal data in accordance with this Policy. If you do not consent to our processing and use of such sensitive personal data, you must not submit such user generated content to our Services.

16\. Your Rights
----------------

* **Opt-out.** You may contact us anytime to opt-out of: (i) direct marketing communications; (ii) automated decision-making and/or profiling; (iii) our collection of sensitive personal data; (iv) any new processing of your personal data that we may carry out beyond the original purpose; or (v) the transfer of your personal data outside the EEA. Please note that your use of some of the Services may be ineffective upon opt-out.
* **Access.** You may access the information we hold about you at any time via your profile/account or by contacting us directly.
* **Amend.** You can also contact us to update or correct any inaccuracies in your personal data.
* **Move.** For the subset of your personal data that is portable, you have the flexibility to move that data to other service providers as you wish.
* **Erase and forget.** (Applicable to EEA and California residents only) In certain situations, for example when the information we hold about you is no longer relevant or is incorrect, you can request that we erase your data. Your request may be denied if the sponsoring organization paying for your access to our Service requires us to retain your information.

If you wish to exercise any of these rights, please contact us using the contact information in Section 18 below. In your request, please make clear: (i) what personal data is concerned; and (ii) which of the above rights you would like to enforce. For your protection, we may only implement requests with respect to the personal data associated with the name and particular email address(es) that you use to send us your request, and we may need to verify your identity before implementing your request. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable and in any event, within one month of your request. Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions that you began prior to requesting such change or deletion.

If you are a resident of California, please [click here](https://support.citiprogram.org/s/article/California-Consumer-Privacy-Act-CCPA-Privacy-Notice) for information regarding your rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act.

17\. Complaints
---------------

We are committed to resolve any complaints about our collection or use of your personal data. If you would like to make a complaint regarding this Policy or our practices in relation to your personal data, please contact us at [privacy@citiprogram.org](mailto:privacy@citiprogram.org) or using the contact information in section 18 below. We will reply to your complaint as soon as we can and in any event, within 45 days. We hope to resolve any complaint brought to our attention, however if you feel that your complaint has not been adequately resolved, you reserve the right to contact your local, regional, or national data protection supervisory authority.

18\. Contact Information
------------------------

We welcome your comments or questions about this Policy. You may contact us at:

Privacy Concerns: [privacy@citiprogram.org](mailto:privacy@citiprogram.org)

Security Concerns:< [security@citiprogram.org](mailto:security@citiprogram.org)

Telephone: 888.529.5929 (U.S.) or +1.305.907.3351 (outside U.S.)

Postal Address:  
CITI Program, a division of BRANY  
101 NE 3rd Avenue, Suite 320  
Fort Lauderdale, FL 33301

* * *

Other Legal
-----------

[

](https://about.citiprogram.org/)

### About Us

### Organizations

### Learners

### Support

### Legal

* 888.529.5929 / 9:00 a.m. to 7:00 p.m. / U.S. Eastern Time / Monday – Friday

[

](https://www.brany.com/)[

](https://protocolbuilderpro.com/)[

](https://thehrpconsultinggroup.com/)[

](https://www.techsoftware.com/)

We use cookies on our website to give you the most relevant experience by remembering your preferences and repeat visits. By clicking “Accept”, you consent to the use of ALL cookies on this website. Please review our [Privacy Notice](https://about.citiprogram.org/privacy-policy/) for more details or click "Cookie Settings" to manage your cookie preferences.  

Cookie SettingsAccept

Manage Cookie Consent

Close

#### Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.

Necessary

 Necessary

Always Enabled

Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. These cookies ensure basic functionalities and security features of the website, anonymously.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| BUY\_NOW |     | This cookie is set to transfer purchase details to our learning management system. |
| CART\_COUNT |     | This cookie is set to enable shopping cart details on the site and to pass the data to our learning management system. |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-advertisement | 1 year | The cookie is set by GDPR cookie consent to record the user consent for the cookies in the category "Advertisement". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-analytics | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Analytics". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-functional | 11 months | The cookie is set by GDPR cookie consent to record the user consent for the cookies in the category "Functional". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-necessary | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookies is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Necessary". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-others | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Other. |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-performance | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Performance". |
| JSESSIONID | session | Used by sites written in JSP. General purpose platform session cookies that are used to maintain users' state across page requests. |
| PHPSESSID | session | This cookie is native to PHP applications. The cookie is used to store and identify a users' unique session ID for the purpose of managing user session on the website. The cookie is a session cookies and is deleted when all the browser windows are closed. |
| viewed\_cookie\_policy | 11 months | The cookie is set by the GDPR Cookie Consent plugin and is used to store whether or not user has consented to the use of cookies. It does not store any personal data. |
| XSRF-TOKEN | session | The cookie is set by Wix website building platform on Wix website. The cookie is used for security purposes. |

Functional

 functional

Functional cookies help to perform certain functionalities like sharing the content of the website on social media platforms, collect feedbacks, and other third-party features.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| bcookie | 2 years | This cookie is set by linkedIn. The purpose of the cookie is to enable LinkedIn functionalities on the page. |
| lang | session | This cookie is used to store the language preferences of a user to serve up content in that stored language the next time user visit the website. |
| lidc | 1 day | This cookie is set by LinkedIn and used for routing. |
| pll\_language | 1 year | This cookie is set by Polylang plugin for WordPress powered websites. The cookie stores the language code of the last browsed page. |

Performance

 performance

Performance cookies are used to understand and analyze the key performance indexes of the website which helps in delivering a better user experience for the visitors.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_gat | 1 minute | This cookies is installed by Google Universal Analytics to throttle the request rate to limit the colllection of data on high traffic sites. |

Analytics

 analytics

Analytical cookies are used to understand how visitors interact with the website. These cookies help provide information on metrics the number of visitors, bounce rate, traffic source, etc.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_ga | 2 years | This cookie is installed by Google Analytics. The cookie is used to calculate visitor, session, campaign data and keep track of site usage for the site's analytics report. The cookies store information anonymously and assign a randomly generated number to identify unique visitors. |
| \_gat\_UA-33803854-1 | 1 minute | This is a pattern type cookie set by Google Analytics, where the pattern element on the name contains the unique identity number of the account or website it relates to. It appears to be a variation of the \_gat cookie which is used to limit the amount of data recorded by Google on high traffic volume websites. |
| \_gat\_UA-33803854-7 | 1 minute | This is a pattern type cookie set by Google Analytics, where the pattern element on the name contains the unique identity number of the account or website it relates to. It appears to be a variation of the \_gat cookie which is used to limit the amount of data recorded by Google on high traffic volume websites. |
| \_gcl\_au | 3 months | This cookie is used by Google Analytics to understand user interaction with the website. |
| \_gid | 1 day | This cookie is installed by Google Analytics. The cookie is used to store information of how visitors use a website and helps in creating an analytics report of how the website is doing. The data collected including the number visitors, the source where they have come from, and the pages visted in an anonymous form. |
| \_hjAbsoluteSessionInProgress | 30 minutes | No description available. |
| \_hjFirstSeen | 30 minutes | This is set by Hotjar to identify a new user’s first session. It stores a true/false value, indicating whether this was the first time Hotjar saw this user. It is used by Recording filters to identify new user sessions. |
| \_hjid | 1 year | This cookie is set by Hotjar. This cookie is set when the customer first lands on a page with the Hotjar script. It is used to persist the random user ID, unique to that site on the browser. This ensures that behavior in subsequent visits to the same site will be attributed to the same user ID. |
| \_hjIncludedInPageviewSample | 2 minutes | No description available. |
| \_hjIncludedInSessionSample | 2 minutes | No description available. |
| \_hjTLDTest | session | No description available. |
| \_uetsid | 1 day | This cookies are used to collect analytical information about how visitors use the website. This information is used to compile report and improve site. |
| BrowserId | 1 year | This cookie is used for registering a unique ID that identifies the type of browser. It helps in identifying the visitor device on their revisit. |
| CFID | session | This cookie is set by Adobe ColdFusion applications. This cookie is used to identify the client. It is a sequential client identifier, used in conjunction with the cookie "CFTOKEN". |
| CFTOKEN | session | This cookie is set by Adobe ColdFusion applications. This cookie is used to identify the client. It provides a random-number client security token. |
| CONSENT | 16 years 5 months 4 days 4 hours | These cookies are set via embedded youtube-videos. They register anonymous statistical data on for example how many times the video is displayed and what settings are used for playback.No sensitive data is collected unless you log in to your google account, in that case your choices are linked with your account, for example if you click “like” on a video. |
| vuid | 2 years | This domain of this cookie is owned by Vimeo. This cookie is used by vimeo to collect tracking information. It sets a unique ID to embed videos to the website. |

Advertisement

 advertisement

Advertisement cookies are used to provide visitors with relevant ads and marketing campaigns. These cookies track visitors across websites and collect information to provide customized ads.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| bscookie | 2 years | This cookie is a browser ID cookie set by Linked share Buttons and ad tags. |
| IDE | 1 year 24 days | Used by Google DoubleClick and stores information about how the user uses the website and any other advertisement before visiting the website. This is used to present users with ads that are relevant to them according to the user profile. |
| MUID | 1 year 24 days | Used by Microsoft as a unique identifier. The cookie is set by embedded Microsoft scripts. The purpose of this cookie is to synchronize the ID across many different Microsoft domains to enable user tracking. |
| test\_cookie | 15 minutes | This cookie is set by doubleclick.net. The purpose of the cookie is to determine if the user's browser supports cookies. |
| VISITOR\_INFO1\_LIVE | 5 months 27 days | This cookie is set by Youtube. Used to track the information of the embedded YouTube videos on a website. |
| YSC | session | This cookies is set by Youtube and is used to track the views of embedded videos. |
| yt-remote-connected-devices | never | These cookies are set via embedded youtube-videos. |
| yt-remote-device-id | never | These cookies are set via embedded youtube-videos. |

Others

 others

Other uncategorized cookies are those that are being analyzed and have not been classified into a category as yet.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_app\_session | 1 month | No description available. |
| \_gfpc | session | No description available. |
| \_uetvid | 1 year 24 days | No description available. |
| \_zm\_chtaid | 2 hours | No description available. |
| \_zm\_csp\_script\_nonce | session | No description available. |
| \_zm\_cta | 1 day | No description |
| \_zm\_ctaid | 2 hours | No description available. |
| \_zm\_currency | 1 day | No description available. |
| \_zm\_mtk\_guid | 2 years | No description available. |
| \_zm\_page\_auth | session | No description available. |
| \_zm\_sa\_si\_none | session | No description |
| \_zm\_ssid | session | No description available. |
| AnalyticsSyncHistory | 1 month | No description |
| BNI\_persistence | 4 hours | No description available. |
| BrowserId\_sec | 1 year | No description available. |
| CookieConsentPolicy | 1 year | No description |
| cred |     | No description available. |
| f   | never | No description available. |
| L-veVQq | 1 day | No description |
| li\_gc | 2 years | No description |
| owner\_token | 1 day | No description available. |
| PP-veVQq | 1 hour | No description |
| renderCtx | session | This cookie is used for tracking community context state. |
| RL-veVQq | 1 day | No description |
| twine\_session | 1 month | No description available. |
| UserMatchHistory | 1 month | Linkedin - Used to track visitors on multiple websites, in order to present relevant advertisement based on the visitor's preferences. |
| web\_zak | past | No description |
| wULrMv6t |     | No description |
| zm\_aid | past | No description |
| zm\_haid | past | No description |

Save & Accept
